Before we can start any data wrangling,
在开始数据处理之前
we need to load our data into Spark.
我们首先要将数据加载到 Spark 中
In this section, we will take a look at how to do that.
在本节中 我们会学习如何进行该操作
The most common data formats you might come across
最常见的数据格式
are CSV, JSON, HTML, and XML.
包括 CSV JSON HTML 和 XML
A CSV file or comma-separated values file,
CSV 文件或者叫逗号分隔值文件
Each line represents a record where fields are always in
每行代表一个记录 其中每个记录的字段排序相同
the same order defined usually by the first header.
字段名称通常为第一行的数据
As the name suggests,
顾名思义 CSV  或者 逗号分隔值文件
the records are separated with a comma.
每行数据都用逗号分隔
This might be problematic though if the records can contain commas as well.
但如果记录的字段也包含逗号的话就可能会出现问题
So oftentimes, the records are wrapped in quotes,
所以记录通常都用引号括起来
or alternative separators actualism.
或用其他分隔符来分隔值
There is no standard for CSV files.
CSV文件没有标准
So different libraries provide a different degree of support to handle such cases,
所以不同的库会提供不同程度的支持
such as new like characters within a record.
例如记录中的换行符
JSON or JavaScript object notation storage records in attribute value pairs.
JSON 或 JavaScript Object Notation 通过键值来存储数据
The values may contain simple often numeric types or arrays.
值可能是简单的数字类型或数组类型
By JSON was derived from JavaScript is a language
尽管 JSON 派生于 JavaScript
independent human-readable format.
但它完全独立于编程语言 同时易于阅读
JSON is very commonly used for browser server communication.
浏览器和服务器之间数据传输常用 JSON 格式
So web server log files often contain this format.
因此 网络服务器日志文件通常包含此格式
HTML or hypertext markup language,
HTML 或超文本标记语言
is a standard markup language for creating web pages and web applications.
是用于创建网页和网络应用程序的标准标记语言
If you scrape data from the Internet,
如果你从互联网上爬取数据
you will need to update HTML.
就需要处理 HTML
An HTML page consists of type input commands
HTML 页面包含标记符
and the texts are marked by angle brackets.
标记符文本用尖括号标记
There are different texts to represent images,
图像、
links, and other specifics of the content.
链接以及其他内容的标记符是不同的
You can think of XML or extensible markup language,
XML 也称 可扩展标记语言
as a generalized version of HTML where the tags don't have a specific meaning.
你可以把它看作为 HTML 的泛化版本  XML 的标记符没有特定含义
Within XML, you can define your own tags to
在 XML 中你可以定义自己的标记符
encode the information in both a machine and human readable.
来编码机器和人都可读的信息
The difficulty of dealing with HTML and XML files is that amines can be nested.
处理 HTML 和 XML 文件的难点在于元素都可以嵌套
So why we process these files,
所以当我们处理这些文件时
we need to keep track of all the opening tags
我们需要记录开始的标记符
we have seen to preserve the structure.
才能获取文件的结构